ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1990 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  2-1-1990 to 2-28-1990
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  1/10/1990 to 1/31/1990
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1990 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  1-1-1990 to 1-9-1990
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1990 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1989 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Opinion of Fourth Circuit, Butzner,J., 1980 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Board Decision JD-871-77, 1980-1982 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Petition for Certiorari, 1977-1980 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Union's Brief to 4th Circuit, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. 2nd Circuit Compliance, 1978-1982 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens, Inc. Correspondence, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  June-July 1983
- J.P. Stevens & Company 11-CA-6077 Wallace, N.C. Remand to Board, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I v. NLRB & ACTWU no.79-1247,79-1254 4th Circuit, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Sledge, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Remand to Board, 1972-1981 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Current Events, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Post-Settlement Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Remand to Board-Statements of Position, 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Wallace, N.C. 79-1502 Fourth Circuit After Remand by Supreme Court, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1983 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  May 1983
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Shop Seniority Problem (Sledge), 1984 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. NLRB RR I 4th Circuit Motion to Consolidate, for Hearing and Rehearing, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Sale of High Point Plant, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. NLRB RR I Motion & Responses, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Sledge Facts Notes, 1979-1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Litigation Expenses Remand to NLRB Cases, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Sledge Plaintiff's Submission of Documents of Record (Volume I of III), 1971 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Sledge Plaintiff's Submission of Documents of Record (Volume II of III), 1971 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. Sledge Plaintiff's Submission of Documents of Record (Volume III of III), 1971 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Remand to Board Papers, 1974-1982 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Company Briefs Notations RR I 4th Circuit, 1974-1975 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Union's Reply Brief to 4th Circuit, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Research-unsorted, 1975-1979 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Wrap-Up, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids - Contract and Side Letters, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. v. ACTWU Briefs, Exceptions, 1976-1977 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. RR I Post-Board Decision Motions, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Pension, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Settlement- News Release, 1978-1980 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-9013, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-8778, 1979-1980 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-7972, 8647, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1988 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1988 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- Sledge GK, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1988 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. GK, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1981 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1976 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Sledge, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  12/21/1989
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1976 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Rosanne Kieper - Notes and Minutes Kootsouradis, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Kootsouradis, et. Al Brookevale Mfg. Co. and ACTWU W.D. PA 84-1025 84-1104, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Target Sportswear (Brookevale Mfg.) Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Brookevale (Target Industries) Monessan, PA Grid Descrip., 1981 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Target - Negotiations, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. Brookevale et al., 1982 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. Brookevale et al. Plaintiffs' Grievances, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  1/83 - 4/83
- Kootsouradis II Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Kootsouradis et al. Chronology, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- John Dohanich Notes Brookevale Kootsouradis, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Anne Marie Harber. Notes and Minutes Kootsouradis, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Brookevale Mfg. Co. Inc. - Collective Bargaining Agreements Target, 1975-1984 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Alice Makel's Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. ACTWU Notes from Arile Brown, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. ACTWU et al. Notes of Meetings- local negotiations - union meetings, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Kootsouradis, 1983-1989 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Kootsouradis II, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. Brookevale Mfg. Co. and ACTWU Court Papers 84-1025, 84-1104, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Kootsouradis I Volume III Formal Papers [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Kootsouradis I Volume III Formal Papers [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Kootsouradis I Volume IV Formal Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Kootsouradis I Volume II Formal Papers [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Kootsouradis I Volume II Formal Papers [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Kootsouradis I Volume I Formal Papers [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Kootsouradis I Volume II Formal Papers [folder 2 of 2[, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Kootsouradis II Formal Papers [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Kootsouradis II Formal Papers [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Kootsouradis Volume II Formal Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- D & D Shirt Company Bonus Pay, 1988-1991 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Derby Cap 9-CA-23458 & 9-CA-23881, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Derby Cap Manufacturing Co., Inc Case Nos. 9-CA-23458 & 9-CA-23881, 1984-1988 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Derby Cap Mfg., Company, Inc. Young Discharge no.9-CA-30454 Louisville, KY, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Dorr Woolen Company Legal, 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Custom Colors, Inc. (Arb) Discharge of Charley Young, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Davol Incorporated Case no.17-RC-10746, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Dayton Industries Discharge of Angela Jones Chicago, Ill. (Local 1771), 1987 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- D&D Shirt, Star Systems, Inc. & Paul Dasher WARN action, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Circuit City Stores, 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Cone Mills Corporation Marie E. Darr, 1985-1987 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Cone Mills (Marie E. Darr), 1986-1987 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Frank Chervan, Inc. Case no.5-CA-17608, 1985-1988 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Circuit City (Negotiations), 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Capital Plastics of Ohio Case no.8-CB-7144, 1991-1992 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Can-Tex Hourly Employees Pension Plan, 1982-1986 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Capital Dye Works Amended Disclosure Statement, 1989-1992 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Catholic Archbishop of California and California Joint Board Files, 1991-1992 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Caleb v. Smith & Sons of Ohio, 1974-1988 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Atmore, Ala. (Christmas Bonus), 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Case no.4-CA-11657, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Case no.15-CA-7956, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- C.H. Masland & Sons 1983 Police Case, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Richard L. Gardner, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Pension Materials, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Reinstatement Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Case no.4-CA-12119, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Local 1882 Atmore, Alabama 15-RD-409, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- C.H. Masland & Sons, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Atmore, Alabama Case no.15-CB-1828, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Case no.6-RC-8653, 1979-1980 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Henry Wade Cox, 1976-1982 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Civil Action no.80-0655-P (S.D. Ala.), 1980-1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- C.H. Masland & Sons Case no.6-RC-8354, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- CMA & ACTWU Negotiations, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Masland (Canadian Plant), 1981 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Farris Fashions, Inc. 8th Circuit Case Brief, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- California Joint Board Athearn, Inc. 21-CA-24968, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Elder Manufacturing Company, 1988-1992 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Objections to Referendum Election of 1981 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Englander Bedding Case no.6-RC-10500, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Englander Bedding Company Case no.6-CA-23016, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- EPE Case no.5-CA-18481, 1991-1992 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- 1983 Referendum Election (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Conway Mill, Inc. Division of United Merchants Case no.11-CA-11978, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Conway Mill- Edna Blaton, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Conway Mill Diane Dunlap Discharge Conway, South Carolina, 1983-1985 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Conway Mill Case no.11-CA-11153 Exceptions, Briefs, Notes, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Conway Mill Case no.11-CA-11153 Decision of ALJ, Briefs to ALJ, Complaint, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Conway Mill, UM&M (Betty Caines-Unemployment HRG), 1985 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Conway Mill (UM&M) Legal Research 11-CA-11153, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Conway Mills, Inc. Johnson 11-CA-11297, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Conway Mills, 11-CA-11,153 Statements, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Conway Exhibits 11-CA-11,153, 1978-1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Conway Mills Discharge of Thurmon White, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Conway Mill UM&M, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Conway Mills UM&M 11-CA-11153 284 NLRB no.18 4th Circuit Appeal, 1987-1988 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Conway Mills Case no.11-CA-11153, 1984-1985 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Conway Mills, Inc. Discharge of Thurmon White no.11-CA-11960, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Grasty Depositions, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Grasty Material, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Grasty Decision (1 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Grasty Decision (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Grasty Decision (3 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Grasty Complaint Local 80 Cash Reports, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Cleveland Joint Board & Joseph Feiss Co. - Emilia Caraballo Discharge, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Chicago & Central States Joint Board General, 1984-1989 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Grasty Depositions, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1976-1989 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Cleveland Joint Board Esther Candusso (Local 768) Vacation Pay Grievance, 1987-1988 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Glove Cities Area Gates Mills, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1974-1989 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Hollytex Carpet Mills FOIA Request, 1979-1987 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Hollytex Case #21-CB-8437, 1983-1987 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Hermans Sporting Goods Arbitration, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Greco Brothers New England, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Hallmark Emblems, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Grasty v. ACTWU, 1986-1991 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- India Ink 21-CA-24459 Copies of Discharge/Warning Cases, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- India Ink Southern California Joint Board, 1979-1985 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- India Ink, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- India Ink Case no.21-CA-24459,24504, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Cleveland Joint Board Complaint of Margaret Ann Houston, 1988-1989 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Health-Tex (Maine Plants) Contracting Out, 1980-1982 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Maine Plants Contracting, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- India Ink 21-CA-24652 and 21-RC-17741, 1986-1988 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Headwear (Clothing Hatters) Cap Industry Fund Minneapolis, St. Paul, MN, 1983-1985 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Amelia Sanders and Levi-Strauss Arbitration, 1986-1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Amelia Sanders v. Levi-Strauss & ACTWU- Depositions of Maggie Flowers, Douglas Ramey, and Ray Quintero, 1987-1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19102, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Laminates, Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-18393 Baltimore, MD, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-6070, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19183, 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19280, 1987-1988 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-18928, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19593, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Laminates Unlimited, Inc. Case no.5-CA-19752, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- H&M Manufacturing & Local 169, 1986-1990 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Amelia Sanders v. Levi Strauss and Company, et al. Co. Responses to Discovery, 1986-1994 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Local 324 Insurance Fund Minutes of the Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1963-1974 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Local 324 (Insurance Fund) [folder 1 of 3], 1980-1986 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Local 324 (Insurance Fund) [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1976 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Local 324 (Insurance Fund) [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1976 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Life-Like Products Inc. Case no.5-RC-13130, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Life-Like Products, Inc. Case no.5-CA-20067, 1988-1989 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Life-Like Products, Inc. Case no.5-CA-20078, 1988-1989 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Kravet Fabric, Inc. Case no.29-RC-6699, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Klote International Corp. Case no.10-CA-22327, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Klote International Case no.10-CA-24009, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Klote International- Grift Grievance, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Kluger Company, Inc. Ben Kluger no.21-RC-17774, 1986-1987 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Klote International Corp. Case no.10-CA-22433, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Lincoln Brass (Jacksboro, TN), 1988-1991 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Magla Libel, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Magla Products, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12183, 1986-1987 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- McAdoo Manufacturing Co., 1987-1989 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- McTague Negotiations, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Mail Well Envelope Co. v. Local 1800, ACTWU- Petition to Vacate Arbitration Award, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Mail Well Envelope Case no.3-CB-5186, 5238 Michael Cancilla, 1987-1988 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Mail-Well Envelope Rochester, New York Contract Proposals/ EAP question, 1987-1988 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Mail-Well Envelope v. ACTWU Local 1800, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- M. Lowenstein Enforcement D.C. Circuit 11-CA-10425, 1982-1986 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- M. Lowenstein Corp. Election Objection Doblin Co. Case no.11-RC-4999, 1981-1982 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- M. Lowenstein Affiliate Case no.11-RC-4999 Doblin Company, 1981-1984 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- M. Lowenstein (General File), 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- M. Lowenstein & Sons, Inc. Eunice Bachman v. ACTWU, 1978-1981 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- M. Lowenstein Corporation (Doblin) Contract, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- M. Lowenstein Case Nos. 11-CA-11464 Michael Ball/Danny Alexander, 1984-1986 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- M. Lowenstein (Doblin Plant) Morganton, N.C. (Affidavits), 1981 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- M. Lowenstein Corporation Case no.11-CA-10425 Summary Judgment, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- M. Lowenstein Corp. Case no.11-RD-422, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- M. Lowenstein (Rock Hill), 1982-1985 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- M. Lowenstein Negotiations, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- M. Lowenstein Corporation Case no.11-CA-11316 Morganton, N.C., 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- M. Lowenstein Corp. 11-CA-104011, 1981-1983 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- M. Lowenstein & Sons Inc. Local 254 (Eunice Bachman), 1979-1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- M. Lowenstein Corp. 11-Ca-10648 (Statements), 1983 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- M. Lowenstein Pension Plan, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mills Case no.11-RC-5726, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-CA-12685, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Monterey Mills, Inc. Case no.26-RC-6784, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Monterey Mills, Inc. Cowan, Tennessee, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Monterey Mills, Inc. Cowan, TN, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Monterey Mills & Local 777 Timothy Cerny Beck Request, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Monterey Mills - William Short, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-CA-12716, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mills Case no.11-CA-14075, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Monterey Mills (FMCS Notice), 1990 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Monterey Mills, Inc. Cowan, Tennessee 26-RC-6909, 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Monterey Mills - Wage Dispute, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Monterey Mills, Inc. Case no.30-CA-12198, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Monterey Mills of Tennessee - Maintenance Mechanic & Picking, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- Jan Mock v. ACTWU & Local 2533 Case no.11-CB-1760, 1989-1990 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- M.U. Industries, Inc. Case no.18-CA-9118, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 21)
- M.U. Industries, Inc. Case no.18-RD-1665, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 22)
- M.U. Industries, Inc. Case no.18-CA-9118, 1985-1987 (Box 96, Folder 23)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-RC-5473, 1988-1990 (Box 96, Folder 24)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-CA-12801, 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 25)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-CA-12610, 1988-1990 (Box 96, Folder 26)
- Mt. Holly Spinning Mill Case no.11-CA-12657, 1988-1990 (Box 96, Folder 27)
- Master Slacks, Corporation Case no.26-CA-4924, et al. Memo on Blocking Charges, 1982-1986 (Box 96, Folder 28)
- Max Kahn Curtain Corporation Bonus & Agreement, 1986-1990 (Box 96, Folder 29)
- Mar-Lyn Mfg. Co. Toxey, AL Cases: 15-CA-10879, 15-CA-11025, 15-CA-11115 Compliance, 1989-1981 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Master Slack Corp. 271 NLRB no.15, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- NLRB v. Master Slacks 6th Circuit Application for Enforcement 84-5387, 1984-1985 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Maremont (Pension Plan), 1980-1981 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Manhattan Sponging Work, Inc. Exhibits, 1989-1990 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Somersworth, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Somersworth, Inc. Bankruptcy, 1984-1992 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Somersworth, Inc. General, 1984-1991 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Manhattan Sponging Works Transcripts, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Skydyne Co. Case no.2-CA-18408, 1983-1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Skydyne (Brooks & Perkins) 2-RM-1985, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Saco Defense Mandatory Exercise Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Roth-Lebaron-Ratner California Joint Board, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Rob Roy, Inc. Cambridge Md. Plant Removal, 1985-1988 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Rob Roy- Seniority Case No. 84-9B-MC, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Rob Roy, Inc. No. 85-2234, 1985-1988 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Rob Roy, Inc., 1988 (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Rob Roy, Cambridge, Maryland Circuit Court (Porchester County) Court Documents, Agreements, 1985-1991 (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Rob Roy Civil Action JH-85-2815, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Rob Roy, Inc. Plant Removal Arbitration, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Rob Roy Import Agreement, 1979-1981 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Rob Roy, Cambridge, Maryland Cutting Rm-Remval/Centralization, 1984-1986 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Rainbow Apparel, Mfg. Company Unfair Labor Practice Charge, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Rapid American, 1973-1986 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- RM Engineered Products, Inc. Discharge of Alfred Reese, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Rainbow Apparel Mfg. Company Case no.15-CA-10512-2 Crestview, Florida, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Rainbow Apparel Mfg. Company ULP Charges, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Rainbow Apparel Crestview, Fla. 15-CA-10590, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Rainbow Apparel Manufacturing Co. Unfair Labor Practice Charges, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Rainbow Apparel Mfg., Co. Case no.15-CA-10663 Crestview, Florida, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Pizza Blends, Inc. Case no.36-RC-5128, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Pizza Blends, Inc. Case Nos. 26-CA-6114, 36-CA-6115, 26-CA-6116, 1988-1990 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- RM Engineered Products, 1986-1989 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Weatherbee Coat, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Tommy Watts & Local 170 Case no.11-CB-1450, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Weatherbee Bankruptcy, 1986-1987 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Weishaar Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Weishaar Yvonne Files, 1984-1986 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Winsome Togs, Inc. & Local 169, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Winsome Togs, Inc. & Local 169, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Wonderknit Company Galax Virginia, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Wonderknit Company Case no.5-CA-18982, 1987-1990 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Wonderknit Company Case no.5-CA-18473, 1986-1988 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- McGregor Corporation Wonderknit Case no.5-CA-17168, 1985-1986 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Wonderknit McGregor Doniger Case no.5-CB-5184, 1985-1987 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Wonderknit Division of McGregor Corp. v. ACTWU, et al. 87-0177-A, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Wonderknit Scoreboard Warn Notice, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Whiteville Apparel Case no.11-CB-2084 Tammy Sykes, 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Whiteville Apparel Corp. Waiting Time Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Zody's (General), 1986-1988 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Zody's Bankruptcy, 1982-1986 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Zody's Closing, 1985-1988 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Nasco-Bankruptcy, 1988-1991 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Nasco Bankruptcy, 1989-1991 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- AMFESCO Bankruptcy AFS, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- NASCO P.R., Inc. Case #89-03988 Chapter 11, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Amfesco Industries, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Amfesco Campbell Group 420 E. Corp. (Guanica Plant), 1982-1988 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- ACTWU AMFESCO Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1986-1988 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- ACTWU AMFESCO Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1989 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- AMFESCO Campbell Extras, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- AMFSECO - Bankruptcy, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- State Mutual Group Coverages, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- AMFESCO- Unfair Labor Practices, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  In Spanish
- AFS Sportshoes Case No. 24-CA-5544, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Amfesco Industries Chapter 11, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- AFS Puerto Rico Bankruptcy, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- AFS Sportshoes, Inc. Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1985-1988 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- AFS-ECO Info, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- AFS Sportshoes CBA, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Amfesco Industries, Inc. Economic Information, 1984-1987 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- AFS Sportshoes, Inc. Refusal to Supply Information Case no.24-CA-5324, 1985-1987 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Dupont de Nemours Company RC case 6-RC-10139 6-CA-21738, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Elbeco, Inc. Meyersdale Manufacturing Co. [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Elbeco, Inc. Meyersdale Manufacturing Co. [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 104, Folder 6)